{"data":[{"question":"When I first met him he _______ (work) in a restaurant.","a":"were working","b":"was working","c":"were workying","answer":"2","explain":"- Using the past continuous when somebody was in the middle of doing something at a certain time in the past (when I first met him)\n- S + was\/ were + V-ing ....","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"11","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"6"},{"question":"Tom _______ (sit) in a corner with a book. I told him that he _______ (read) in very bad light.","a":"was sitting\/was reading","b":"was siting\/were reading","c":"were sitting\/were reading","answer":"1","explain":"- Using the past continuous to say that somebody was in the middle of doing something at a certain time in the past","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"11","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"6"},{"question":"Who you _______ (talk) to on the telephone as I came in? I _______ (talk) to Mr.Pitt.","a":"was you talking\/was talking","b":"were you talking\/was talking","c":"were you talking\/were talking","answer":"2","explain":"- Using the past continuous to say that somebody was in the middle of doing something at a certain time in the past","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"11","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"6"},{"question":"She _______ (stand) at the bus stop. I asked her what bus she _______ (wait) for.","a":"was standing\/were waiting","b":"were standing\/were waiting","c":"was standing\/was waiting","answer":"3","explain":"- Using the past continuous to say that somebody was in the middle of doing something at a certain time in the past","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"11","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"6"},{"question":"I went into the garden to see what the boys _______ (do). James _______(weed) and Alexander _______(cut) the grass.","a":"were doing\/was weeding\/was cutting","b":"were doing\/was weeding\/was cuting","c":"were doing\/were weeding\/was cutting","answer":"1","explain":"- Using the past continuous to say that somebody was in the middle of doing something at a certain time in the past","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"11","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"6"},{"question":"The car had nobody in it but the engine _______ (run).","a":"were running","b":"was running","c":"was runing","answer":"2","explain":"- Using the past continuous to say that something was in the middle of an action at a certain time in the past","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"11","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"6"},{"question":"Are you going to Rome? I thought that you _______ (go) to Milan.","a":"were going","b":"was going","answer":"1","explain":"- Using the past continuous to say that somebody was in the middle of doing something at a certain time in the past","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"11","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"7"},{"question":"The traffic _______ (make) so much noise that I couldn't hear what he _______(say).","a":"were making\/were saying","b":"was making\/was saing","c":"was making\/were saying","d":"was making\/was saying","answer":"4","explain":"- he\/it + was + V-ing.\n- make -> making.\n- say -> saying.","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"11","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"5"},{"question":"The house was in great disorder because he _______ (redecorate) it.","a":"were redecorating","b":"was redecorating","c":"was redecorateing","answer":"2","explain":"- Using the past continuous to say that somebody was in the middle of doing something at a certain time in the past","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"11","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"6"},{"question":"Just as I _______ (wonder) what to do next, the phone rang.","a":"was wondering","b":"were wondering","c":"wes wondering","answer":"1","explain":"- Using the past continuous to say that somebody was in the middle of doing something at a certain time in the past","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"11","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"6"}]}